SIOBHAN POWELL

QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

Uptown Chicago, IL • (402) 889-0819 • mail@siobhan.zip https://siobhan.zip

SUMMARY

Junior Quality Assurance Engineer and Department Lead with 7 years of startup experience, generating end-to-end automated testing pipelines & overseeing the implementation of companywide quality assurance protocols. I primarily employ a behavior driven development approach in my case design, and pride myself on translating complex information into easy-to-absorb content.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Quality Assurance Engineer // Rush ReCommerce

September 2022 - April 2024

- · Created and maintained CI/CD regression suites utilizing tools such as Cypress, Docker, Postman, and GitLab, for product processing tools as well as customer facing e-commerce
- · Collaborated with partnered product teams for integrated tools such as Shopify, LogicBroker, & FedEx to ensure coverage for platform stability.
- Established User Acceptance Testing protocol, including generating training material and scheduling demonstrations both virtually and in-person of new and updated feature releases.
- Instituted comprehensive test automation reporting for tracking coverage, performance, and reliability, facilitating data-driven decision making.

Manual Quality Assurance Analyst // Rush ReCommerce

August 2019 - September 2022

- Managed QA sprint planning based on test case generation and automation priorities, allowing for rapid story processing while maintaining documentation and reliability of extant test suites.
- · Utilized SQL and Oracle VM VirtualBox to manage multiple varied testing environments and generated test data collections as needed for custom application testing.
- Generated S.O.P. for hardware and software related testing criteria, and assisted in establishing a consistent company-wide IT hardware management schema for training and quality regulation.
- Facilitated the creation of a Helpdesk Portal & Knowledge Base, including designing SLA structure, agent-on-call roster, intranet standards such as employee hierarchy and newsletter, and all related technical business documentation required for the knowledge base.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- JavaScript
 Git / GitLab
- SQL Selenium
- Postman Playwright
- JIRA Docker
- Cypress Oracle VM VirtualBox
 Google Suite
- Bash
- Linux
- HTML5
- CSS
- User Acceptance Testing
- Behavior-Driven Development
- Agile Methodologies
- Document Control
- Technical Writing

EDUCATION

University of Nebraska-Lincoln Partial Undergrad, Undeclared

August 2015 - June 2016